What should I do?
After three losses, your status as a selector is revoked.
As for your wish, it becomes corrupted.
All I can tell you is her wish was to make friends.
You can imagine what a corruption of that would be.
So you're saying she lost her friends?
Far worse than that.
She can never make friends again.
Horrible, but unfortunately there's more.
With her third loss, not only is her selector status gone...
Hitoi can't read it anymore.
She said that all the words were disappearing.
She also tells me she doesn't remember you.
So are all her memories related to those battles, as if they never even took place.
There has to be something I can do.
Anything!
Please be there.
Kuribayashi residence.
Oh, Ruko.
How are you doing?
I heard you were sick.
Um, hey, is Yuzuki home?
No, she's still out.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Uh, yep, just Peachy.
See ya!
Ruko?
Bro?
めくりめくる楽 目まぐるしいステージで
その絡まった感情 満足いくまで何回も壊してしまえ
運命に手招きされ彷徨う明日は
何を選んで何を手放し 一つになればいいんだろう
なじった毒がおさらす余裕なんてないよ
乾いた後悔の海を飲み干す君は
限られた言葉でいつしかの笑顔 許して欲しいんだろう
現実を忘れたって 構わないよ
だから 今も知らないでいたいな
ご視聴ありがとうございました
1,2,1,2
2,1,2、メイマイラしていない
1,2,1、2,1、2、2、1、3、5、1、2、1、3、8、1 まず
Yuzuki?
No, I haven't seen her today.
Why, is something up?
No!
I summon Amber, and I attack you with it!
Ugh!
Man, if only I pulled guard!
At least tell me what's wrong!
Woo!
Hey, if you're sad, tell me why.
I know!
Let's battle!
A battle will make you happy again!
You'll see.
You just wanted to see me suffer, didn't you?
And I bet you enjoyed it!
You're wrong, that's not true!
It's not true!
So why can't I stop?
Crud, that way's blocked.
Is there another way to reach Akira? I'm having no luck.
Big surprise. What do you need her for?
Well, because she took some outfits home last time.
Are you nuts? Why'd you let her do that?
I'm sorry. She swore she was gonna bring them back, but then we canned her.
Terrific.
Why can't they get in touch with Akira?
Hey, who are you?
Um, I'm a...
You here for a shoot? For which magazine?
Well, it's... or um... it's... it's called...
Oh, there you are.
Huh?
It's okay. She's my guest here tonight.
Oh, she is? Oh geez, no one warned me. Sorry, Iona.
Iona...
Look, I...
You came here because you wanted to battle. Can't fight the urge anymore, can you?
No! You're wrong! I just wanted to see Akira and talk to her about...
That loser? What do you want with her?
Just to talk.
Well, you're too late. She's not here anymore. In fact, I highly doubt we'll ever be seeing her again.
Why?
She lost a battle to us. She lost one to you too, right?
You came here to see what happened to her, didn't you? Make sure she was okay?
Oh, that's so sweet. Then again, maybe you just came here to rub your victory in her stupid face.
That's not funny, okay?
Oh, chill. And by the way, Akira lost to another selector besides you two.
Wait, then that means...
Yep, that makes three losses. So game over, goodbye, and good riddance to bad rubbish.
I... I didn't know. Where is she? Is she okay?
Who cares? But if I had to guess, she's probably crying her eyes out somewhere. Just like your other loser friend did.
What other friend?
The mousy little wallflower with the glasses.
Hichoe? Oh God, what did you do to her?
Same as we did to Akira.
Gave her a beating.
A battle? With me?
Sorry. But Hichoe's wish has already come true. She doesn't need to battle. Thank you both. But no.
Well, if she's already had her wish fulfilled, what does she have to lose? Come on, just one match.
I'm sure you know how important a wish can be. Iona's really giving it her all to have hers come true. It'd mean so much if you helped her out.
She has a point. I already made friends, so no matter how this match goes down, I'm still a winner.
Hichoe...
Alright then, I'll battle you.
Lucky for us, your little four-eyed friend didn't know what would happen if she lost three times.
Wait, you... you knew Hichoe already had two losses but still did it? How could you?
You monsters, that's horrible!
Want to battle us for revenge?
We hurt one of your friends, so I'm sure you want to even the score.
You won't get a better chance than this.
Let's battle!
Even if I did, it won't help Hichoe... or her wish.
And yours?
What?
Your wish. Did you find one?
Well, I...
Aha, so you did.
No, I still don't have one.
Liar.
You know, I remember what you said to me.
That a selector battling without a wish was blasphemy, whatever that means.
Well, it's a good thing I don't have one, because either way, I'll never battle again.
No! Please don't give up, Ru! I love battling with you more than anything! Don't quit now!
Tom, I... sorry. But I'm done. No more.
Tell me, Little Miss Drama Queen. Wanting friends? Being with someone you love? Those are both pretty lame wishes, don't you think?
No! Not at all!
Deep down, you agree, because your wish is a lot more exciting.
I told you, I don't have a wish!
You do. Don't try to hide it, because we know.
How can you tell me that when I don't even know? Why are you saying this stuff?
Because you and I have the same wish. It's that feeling. I love it too.
My life wasn't bad before I started playing, but it wasn't especially good either.
Wh-what do you mean?
I never gave my life much thought. Just accepted it for what it was. Until I found her. And then, that's when I first felt it.
I understood it. I savored that feeling. It gave me purpose. It made me feel truly alive for the very first time. It felt like destiny. Like it was part of my soul. Doing battle is in my blood. In my flesh. In my bones. Do you see? It is my very being.
But, come on. If you lose three times, you suffer a terrible fate. And even if you win, someone else will suffer instead. How is that good?
Perhaps it's not. But it is the nature of battle. And our nature as well. Both mine, and yours.
Is she wrong?
Stop it. Please just don't…
Why not be honest with yourself? I know you've felt it. And once you have, there's no way you can ever quit.
Say what you like, but you still yearn for it. You lust for battle. For victory.
I want nothing more than to battle you. And you me?
I do. Yay! Yes, I'd like to battle you. I really would. Badly. But you see…
Open!
What's the matter? We both heard you. You said you wanted to battle.
But that's not what I meant!
You didn't let me finish!
Sorry, was there something else?
Who cares? Forget it and have some fun!
Good. Now let's do this thing.
Battle!
Hey, Will!
This is just sad.
Even your pal Hitoi put up more of a fight
and you know how pathetic she is.
A spell to search for low-level cards?
Why would she use that now?
I don't get it.
Something's not right here.
Why is she only using low-level attacks?
Time to grow!
Wake up, Gru!
It's time to get serious!
Nice move, Yona.
Yona!
Wake up, Gru!
It's time to get serious!
Nice move, Yona.
If you could see what cards were missing from your deck, you could find out which ones were used for your life cloth.
As a result, if Ruko attacks now...
Tama, don't attack! Just end the turn early!
What?
Oh, too bad.
Your move!
Spell, blessed reminiscence!
I knew it!
Alright!
Arch-ambi spell!
Yeah!
Woo!
Well played, Tama!
I knew it!
So, how long can you keep fighting like this?
Long as it takes!
Forever!
Forever?
I don't know what that word means!
It means for all time!
Oh, it does?
Then yes!
Of course!
I want to battle forever!
It's a word!
How about you?
Yuzuki...
Over there...
A selector...
Uh...
Huh?
It's her.
Where's Iona?
The dressing room, I guess.
Well, instead of guessing, go find her and bring her in here.
Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
Yes. She's definitely the one.
Hey, Iona. What the...
Finally. I found her.
Tama! Wish crisis attack!
At last.
There you are. They're waiting for you in Studio A. They need you there as soon as possible.
Okay. I'll be right there.
That was incredible.
Please tell me you agree.
Uh, well, I, um, maybe, but...
It was great! It's the most fun in the whole world!
I can't wait for the next one! I want to battle these guys forever!
I think quitting was a bad idea. We should do this more!
And you think so too, right, Ru?
Well, what do you say?
You're the one.
No.
We won.
Yeah.
Wonder how many losses she has now.
Ah...
No, I'll go.
But you stay here in case she comes back.
All right.
So this cafe you were saying Ruko went to
with her friend's mom, it's just down the street?
Yes, dear.
She said they were talking and all of a sudden
Rue got upset and just ran out of there.
Weird. Don't know what that's about.
Well, you can ask her later,
because I'm sure Rue's just fine.
What happened back there?
How could I?
I gave in to temptation.
I forgot about my friends.
Forgot about what I did to Akira.
Nothing else mattered.
That was incredible.
Please tell me you agree.
No, I wouldn't.
It's not incredible.
It's scary.
I feel like it's taking me over.
I've got to quit.
No!
Tama, I'm sorry about this.
But I can't battle anymore.
Understand?
Ruko.
Yuzuki!
I...
So, hey, what's up? I'm just, you know...
Did you do it?
Um...
Battle, I mean.
You did.
I did and won, and got this.
Akira wants to meet with us.
Think she's here?
Haniyo, sense anything?
No, nothing.
Ruko.
This girl you faced, what was she like?
She was... well...
Mine was about the same age as me.
I wonder, what wish of hers did I kill?
Yuzuki.
Boo-hoo!
You two get to live the bomb-diggity lives of selectors, but you're all sad and gloomy about how hard it is.
Poor little things.
On one hand, we have super-gross Yuzupu who's in love with her own brother, and on the other, we have Ruru who, like, gets off on Wee Cross battles or something.
Just like, what's her face?
Wait, who do you mean?
What's with the mask?
What, this?
Since you asked, I'll let you see.
Guess it's your lucky day.
A...
Aki-raki
cold
aki-raki
I don't know what it is, but I feel different.
I think it's the end of the road.
Yuzuki? What happened?
Think about how your parents would feel if something happened to you.
I won't end up like her.
No, we're not. This is awful.
Next time, That False Vow.